MIGUEL BOMFIM

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

I have worked as Technical Support, which contributed a lot to improving my problem-solving skills. After 1 year in this area I made a career transition to Frontend development where I have been working for 3 years. My expertise includes **JavaScript**, **React**, among other JavaScript frameworks and libraries.

EXPERIENCES

Compass UOL - Frontend Developer

10/2020 - 06/2023

Development of interactive components and functionalities using the React framework. Web Development. Responsive Design. Version control systems.

HostGator - Technical Support

03/2020 - 10/2020

Customer support. Website hosting configuration.

Intelbras - Technical Support

10/2018 - 03/2019

Customer support. Configuration of CCTV equipment. Network configuration.

PROJECTS

Guided Selling (Project Link)

Project developed for the company Natura & Co. A purchasing guide quiz that at the end indicates a product based on the answers.

TECHNOLOGIES: ReactJS, NextJS, Typescript, JestJS,

Natds-js

Photography Portfolio (<u>Project Link</u>)

TECHNOLOGIES: ReactJS, Typescript

GitHub Api (Project Link)

One of my first study projects, which I intend to evolve.

TECHNOLOGIES: ReactIS

CONTACT

Linkedin: /miguel-bomfim GitHub: /miguel-bomfim Phone: 48 99668-6017

Email: miguelaubom@gmail.com

TECHNOLOGIES

JavaScript (ES6)

React

Next

React Native

Expo

Node

Git / GitHub

Jest

EDUCATION

UNICESUMAR

Analysis and systems development

LANGUAGE

Portuguese (native)

English